# Ketan Parmar CA and M.com

## **SUMMARY**

Highly motivated and result oriented Senior Financial Analyst with approving authority and a strong financial background of 8+ years in a corporate environment. Experienced in a fast-paced, deadline-oriented environment with the ability to research detail, consolidate and translate data as per organization policies.

### **KEY SKILLS:**

Strong Analytical Skills	Deadline and delivery-oriented	Accountability
<ul> <li>Strong IT skills</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Self-driven</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Collaborative</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>Team Leader / handling</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Innovative</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Team player</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>Strong Communication skills</li> </ul>	<ul><li>Integrity</li></ul>	

### **IT SKILLS:**

•	Proficient in Microsoft Excel	<ul><li>FinnOne</li></ul>	<ul> <li>Knowledge of SQL</li> </ul>
•	MS Word and PowerPoint	<ul><li>CAM / CAD</li></ul>	<ul> <li>Tally ERP</li> </ul>
•	MS Excel Macros		

### **EDUCATION:**

•	Chartered Accountant CA	from. The Institute of Chartered Accountant of India	2012
•	Master of Commerce M.com	from. IDOL – University of Mumbai	Apr-2013
•	Bachelors of Commerce B.com	rom. IDOL – University of Mumbai	Apr-2011
•	12th Std	from. Pratap College – Pune Board	Feb 2007
•	10th Std	from. R.G.E.M.S – Pune Board	Feb 2005

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:**

# K Parmar & Associates (Proprietor)

Ahmedabad (2-Dec-2021 To Till Now)

- Arranging loans / finance for clients
- Income Tax Return filing and GST Return consultation
- Tax auditing

## FedBank Financial Services Ltd (FedFina) (Area Credit Manager)

Ahmedabad (7-May-2021 To 1-Dec-2021)

- Locations responsibility Ahmedabad, Rajkot, Pune and Vapi-Valsad belt.
- Present and defend case recommendations to senior leadership team
- Team leading and training on regular basis
- Financial ratio analysis and review its impact on loan performance
- Vendor empanelment on business decision
- Maintain an comprehensive view on Client, sector and industry trends
- Interacting market participants including banks and NBFCs for credit monitoring

## EPI Money Pvt Ltd (Flexi Loans) (Senior Manager Credit and Risk)

Mumbai (1-Dec-2020 To 6-May-2021)

- Approving loan under credit authority and recommending high ticket case
- Underwriting Channel finance, Dealer funding cases
- Close communication with policy team for changes in policy as per changing circumstances

## IDFC First Bank Ltd (Senior Credit Manager)

Pune and Ahmedabad (7-Mar-2014 To 29-Apr-2020)

- Location exposure: Ahmedabad, Pune, Nasik, Rajkot, Bhavnagar, Mehsana, Himmatnagar, Surat and Jamnagar
- Risk underwriting for SME customer of unsecured loans for working capital needs

- Loan sanctioning authority of 25Lacs with mid level deviation authority
- Client interaction i.e. personal discussion (PD) for evaluate business set up, its working, viability and end use of the funds
- Perform quantitative and qualitative analysis
- Preparation of the credit assessment memos (CAM / CAD)
- Portfolio monitoring for of early warning signals to curb early mortality and non-starter cases in organization's assets
- Meeting customer for emi collection
- Guide and train operations team for case processing and disbursement within TAT
- Religare Finvest Ltd (Credit Manager Secured and Unsecured Loans)

Pune (6-May-2013 To 28-Feb-2014)

- Location Exposure: Pune, Nasik and Bangalore
- Underwriting cases of loan against property LAP and Housing loans HL
- Credit of Business loans, Professional loans and Personal loans
- Projection / forecasting of cash flow statements for under-construction projects
- PD with customers for understanding set up, its working, use of the funds and property verification
- Co-ordinating and managing legal and technical vendors quality and timely reports
- Multi location experience Pune, Nasik and Bangalore

#### **CA INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE:**

Mariman Point, Mumabi (30-Jul-2010 TO 05-May-2011)

Minesh Shah & Company, Chartered Accountants (Article Trainee) Charni Road, Mumbai (07-Nov-2007 TO 29-Jul-2010)

## **ACHIVEMENTS AND ADDITIONAL KNOWLEDGE:**

- Winner of Ace Employee of Quarter Award in December 2015
- Achieved top performance in business loan credit team across India & was awarded with Australia trip
- Achieved Band 7 in English Speaking IELTS test in July 2020

## **LANGUAGE:**

EnglishMarathi

Hindi • Gujarati